Composed By / Taka
Lyrics By / Taka
Song By / ONE OK ROCK
"The Beginning"
Just give me a reason to keep my heart beating
Don't worry it's safe right here in my arms
As the world falls apart around us
All we can do is hold on
Hold on
Take my hand
and bring me back
I'll risk everything if it's for you
a whisper into the night
Telling me it's not my time and don't give up
I've never stood up before this time
でも 譲れないもの
握ったこの手は離さない
So Stand up stand up
Just gotta keep it
I wanna wake up wake up
Just tell me how I can
Never give up
狂おしいほど刹那の艶麗
Just tell me why baby
They might call me crazy
for saying I'll fight until there is no more
愁いを含んだ閃光
眼光は感覚的衝動
Blinded I can't see the end
so where do I begin
Say not a word I can hear you
The silence between us
なにもないように映ってるだけ
I'll take this chance and I'll make it mine
ただ隠せないもの
飾ったように見せかけてる
So Stand up stand up
Just gotta keep it
I wanna wake up wake up
Just tell me how I can
Never give up
悲しみと切なさの艶麗
Just give me a reason to keep my heart beating
Don't worry it's safe right here in my arms
くだけて泣いて咲いて
散ったこの思いは
so blinded I can't see the end
Look how far we've made it
The pain I can't escape it
このままじゃまだ
終わらせる事は出来ないでしょ
何度くたばりそうでも
朽ち果てようとも
終わりはないさ
so where do I begin
握りしめた
失わぬようにと…
手を広げればこぼれ落ちそうで
失うものなどなかった
日々の惰性を捨てて
君を…
Just tell me why baby
They might call me crazy
for saying I'll fight until there is no more
愁いを含んだ閃光
眼光は感覚的衝動
Blinded I can't see the end
Look how far we've made it
The pain I can't escape it
このままじゃまだ
終わらせる事は出来ないでしょ
何度くたばりそうでも
朽ち果てようとも
終わりはないさ
It finally begins